Guide to the Artists Space Collection of Artist Files MSS.506
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Gerber, Alison, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Gerou, Daphne, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Gervasi, Santiago, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Gerwin, Daniel, 1994-2002 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Getnick, Brian, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 81)
- Gherardi, Bob, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- Giacalone, Xavier, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- Giancristiano, Michael, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- Gibbons, Charles, 1993-2005 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- Gibbons, Lari, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- Gibson, Jeffrey, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- Gieseke, Lena, 1999-2001 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- Giffin, Matthew, 1980-1986 (Box 60, Folder 50)
- Giglio, John, 1995-1999 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Giglio, Mark, 1995-1997 (Box 63, Folder 82)
- Giladi, Rachel, 2000-2005 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Gilbert, Elliott, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Gilboy, Margaretta, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Gilewicz, Wojciech, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Gilfilen, Beth, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Gill, Iris, 1995-2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Gillespie, Dan, 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Gillespie, Eileen, 1996-2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Gillman, Johanna, 1986-2001 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Gilmore, Dawn, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Gilmore, Kate, 2002-2003 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Gilpatrick, Eleanor, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Ginsberg, Elizabeth, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Ginsburg, Emily, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Ginsburg, Eric, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Giobbi, Chambliss, 1998-2004 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Giordano, Joan, 1984-1989 (Box 60, Folder 69)
- Giovinco, Steve, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Giragosian, Polly, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Giralt, Juanmiguel, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Giron, Frances, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Glass, Margot, 1989-1995 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Glasser, Loie, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Glauer, Elizabeth, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Glazer, Helen, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Gleeson, Madge, 1998-2005 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Glenn, Alan, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Glessner, Virginia, 1989-2003 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Glicksberg, Katie, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Glidden, Madeline, 1994-2003 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Glover, Patrick, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Glynn, David, 1993-1999 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Goble, Jacob, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Goell, Abby, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Goetz, Justin, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Goetz, Monika, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Gofstein, Susan, 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Golan, Dolon, 1999-2000 (Box 63, Folder 83)
- Golbert, Sandra, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 49)
- Gold, Joan, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Gold, Susan, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Goldberg, Barry, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Goldberg, Greg, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Goldberg, Marianne, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 68)
- Goldberg, Neil, 1994-2001 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Goldblatt, Larry Mark, 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Goldfarb, Anders, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Goldfarb, Maximillian, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Goldish, Suzanne, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Goldman, Ben, 1998-2004 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Goldman, Charles, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Goldman, Toby, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 47)
- Goldner, Janet, 1991-2001 (Box 19, Folder 48)
- Goldsmith, Gail, 1988-2001 (Box 19, Folder 49)
- Goldsmith, Lance, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 50)
- Goldsmith, Silvianna, 1995-2001 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Goldstein, Deborah, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 51)
- Goldstein, Eleanor, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 52)
- Goldstein, Pat, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 53)
- Golomb, I Leon, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 54)
- Goncarova, Sarah Beth, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 55)
- Gong, Faith, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 56)
- Gonzalez, Ronald, 1985-1996 (Box 60, Folder 67)
- Good, Jesse, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 57)
- Goode, Dale, 1994-2002 (Box 19, Folder 58)
- Goodfriend, Pennelope, 1994-2001 (Box 19, Folder 59)
- Goodman, Rima, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 60)
- Goodwin, Danny, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 61)
- Goodwin, Joe, 1994-2005 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Goodyear, Jessica, 1996-2003 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Gopinath, Gabrielle, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Gora-Wita, Jolanta, 1990-1995 (Box 60, Folder 66)
- Gordon, Melissa, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Gormley, Brian, 1994-1997 (Box 63, Folder 84)
- Gorski, Kalika, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Gosset, Isabelle, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Goto, Fumiko, 1991-1993 (Box 60, Folder 65)
- Gottesfeld, Linda, 1991-2005 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Gorostiaga, Dan, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Gough, Lee, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Gould, Peter, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Govindnathan, Pallavi, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Goyette, Rebecca, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Grade, John, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Grado, Cathleen, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Graef, William, 1993-2001 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Grafelman, Glenn, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Graham, Dylan, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Graham, Eric, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Graham, Sara, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Grangeon, Jean Mehdi, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Granja, Norberto, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Grant, Anjali, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Grasso, Jennifer, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Graupe Pillard, Grace, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Gray, Barroy, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Gray, Emma, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Gray, Owen, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Greason Rajerison, Elizabeth, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 70)
- Greco, Paul, 1990-2001 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Greek, Deborah, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Greenbaum, Joanne, 1985-1987 (Box 60, Folder 57)
- Greenberg, Max, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Greenberg, Theresa, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Greene, Bryan, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Greene, Jonathan Todd, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Greene, Kira, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Greene, Michelle, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 56)
- Greene, Sean, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Greene, Susanne, 1994-2001 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Greenberg, Bernice, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 85)
- Greenfield, Julie Louise, 1995-2005 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Greengold, Laura, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Gregorio, Peter, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Greig, Cynthia, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Greis, Max, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Grenzini, Alessandro, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 55)
- Greve, Margie, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Grifel, Eti, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Griffin, Chris, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- Griffin, David, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Griffin, Laura, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Griffo, Michela, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Grigoriadis, Mary, 1998-2001 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Grill, Clare, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 48)
- Grogan, Geoff, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 49)
- Grohmann, Helen Lenio, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 50)
- Grossman, Beth, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 51)
- Grostein, Marcia, 1985-1989 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Groux, Nadja, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Grove, Susan Evans, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 86)
- Grubin, Joan, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 53)
- Grubstein, Marc, 1995-2001 (Box 20, Folder 54)
- Grunder, Robert, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 55)
- Grzenkowicz, Yvonne, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 56)
- Gsell, Arnaud, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 57)
- Guarino, Diana, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 87)
- Gubin, Mikhail, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 58)
- Guernsey, Betty, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 59)
- Guerra, Manuel, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 60)
- Guimarey, Carolina, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 61)
- Gulan, Genco, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 62)
- Gundersen, Christina, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 63)
- Gundersen, Joan, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 64)
- Guralnick, Jody, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 65)
- Gurevich, Dalit, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 66)
- Gurvich, Ruth, 1995-1997 (Box 63, Folder 88)
- Gushee, Rhonda, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 67)
- Gustavsson, Patrik, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 68)
- Gute, Charles, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 69)
- Gutierrez, Robert, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 70)
- Gutman, Bertha Steinhardt, 1994-2001 (Box 20, Folder 71)
- Guy, Sharon, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 72)
- Guzman, Erik, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 73)
- Ha, Hyoungsun, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 74)
- Ha, Jooyeon, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 75)
- Haas, Kris, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 76)
- Hackemann, Rebecca, 1999-2002 (Box 20, Folder 77)
- Hadfield, Geoffrey, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Hadfield, Jared, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Hadfield, Pamela, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Haenlein, Nathan, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Haffner, Matt, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Hage, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Hagen, Stefan, 2001-2004 (Box 64, Folder 91)
- Hagy, Kathryn, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Hailey, Michelle, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Hajdamowicz, Lech, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Hakansson/Mayhew, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Hales, David, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Haley, Michael, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Hall, Linda, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Hall, Philip, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Hall, Ronald, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Hallas, Caroline, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Hallman, Terri, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Hallsey, J. Lee, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Halper, Pauline, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Halpern, Cynthia, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Halsey, Gabriela, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Ham, Soomin, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Hamada, Hiroyuki, 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Hamburger, Susan, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Hamer, Katy, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Hamerman, Jesse, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Hamilton, Claibourn, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Hamilton, Lisa, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Hammond, Bryce, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Hammond, Harmony, 1991-2001 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Hampton, Brad, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Han, Christy, 1994-2002 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Han, Debbie, 1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Han, Donna, 1992-1994 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Han, Heng-Gil, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Handal, Roger, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Handelman, Michelle, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Handleman, Janice, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Handley, Joanne, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Handon, G. L., 2003 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Hanke, Jessica, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Hankey, Jessica, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Hanoch, Doron, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Hansen, Elaine, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Hanson, Cooper, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Hanson, Jody, 2000-2002 (Box 63, Folder 89)
- Hansen, Sarah, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Hanudel, Trisha, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Happach, Bozena, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Harder-Lutz, Barbara, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- Harder, Rodney, 1988-1989 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Hardouin, Aurele, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Hardy, Jeanne, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 44)
- Hargrove, Dana, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 45)
- Harington, Elizabeth, 1994-2001 (Box 21, Folder 46)
- Harker, Charles, 1997-2003 (Box 21, Folder 47)
- Harles, Graham, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 48)
- Harlow, Lynne, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 49)
- Harmanus, Stephan, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- Harmon, Jennifer, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 51)
- Harp, Jacquelyn, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 52)
- Harper, Dennis, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 53)
- Harrigan, Jim, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 54)
- Harris, Carla, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 55)
- Harris, Esther, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 56)
- Harris, Jack, 1995-2001 (Box 21, Folder 57)
- Harris, John, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 58)
- Harris, Pamela, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 59)
- Harris, Teresa M., 2002 (Box 21, Folder 60)
- Harris, William, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 61)
- Harrison, Jan, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 62)
- Harrison, Ruthanne, 1989-1997 (Box 63, Folder 91)
- Harrington, David, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 90)
- Hart, Barbara J., 2004 (Box 21, Folder 63)
- Hart, Claudia, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 64)
- Hart, Kevin, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Hartnett, Marilu, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 65)
- Hartung, Oliver, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 66)
- Harvey, Arran, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 67)
- Harvey, Charlotte, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 68)
- Harvey, Julie, 1995-2001 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Harvey, Katharine, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 69)
- Harzinski, Kristofer, 2003-2005 (Box 21, Folder 70)
- Hasbun, Gabriela, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 71)
- Hasekura, Kei, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 75)
- Hashimoto, Koichi, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Hatch, Mary, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Hatter, Richard, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Hatton, Julian, 1993-2001 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Haubon, Daniel, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Haugerud, Grady, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Hauser, Sarah, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Haung, Lu-d, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 76)
- Haven, Shelley, 1988-1999 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Hawke, John, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Hayashi, Toru, 1991-1996 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Hayes, Connie, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Hayes, David, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Hayes, Frederick, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Hayward, Julie, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Hazard, Catherine, 1998-2004 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Heady, Dean, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Heagle, Karen, 1995-1998 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Healy, Colleen, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Healy, Terence, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Heaslip, Patricia, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Hebblethwaite, Paul, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Hecht, Laurel, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Hecht, Lisa, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Hecht, Sheila, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Hei, Khiang, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Heiderer, Susan, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Heidkamp, Daniel, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Heilborn, Marta, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Heinert, Jurgen, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Heinlein, Sabine, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Heinrich, Frances, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Heisen, Paula, 1995-2001 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Heiss, Wes, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Heizman, Matthew, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Held, Archie, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Held, Matt, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Helfant, Hilary, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Heller, Christine, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Hellstrom, Carl, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Hellstrom, Patter, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Hellstrom, Thomas, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Helms, Luke, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Hemingway, Juliette, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Hemphill, Tahir, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Henbest de Calvillo, Jennifer, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Henderson, David, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Henderson, Karen, 1994-2001 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Henderson, Mary, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Henderson, Roderik, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Hendrick, Peter, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Henk, Diane, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Henn, Christa, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Henne, Carolyn, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Hensel, Susan, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Herbert, Richard, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Herman, Molly, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Herman, Rebecca, 2003-2004 (Box 61, Folder 87)
- Hernandez, Monica, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Herrit, Linda, 1992-1996 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Herrmann, Frank, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Herster, Margot, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Herz, Nicole, 1991-1999 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Hesse, Heidi, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Hester, Edward W., 2004 (Box 61, Folder 88)
- Hettmansperger, Sue, 1988-1994 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Hevener, Fillmer, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Hewetson, Hannah, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Hexon, Janese, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Hibit, Eric, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Hickman, Robert, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Hickman, Shannon, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Hicks, Angie, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Hideg, Margit, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Hiebert, Ted, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Higbee, Brian, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Hightower, Stephen, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Hiiva, Olga, 1992-1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Hildebrand, Peter, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Hildebrandt, Bernhard, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Hill, Amy, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Hill, Daniel, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Hill, Edwin, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Hill, Houston, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Hill, Kenneth, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Hill, Maggie, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Hill, Mike, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Hills, Ria, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Hilson, Doug, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Hilton, Gregory, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Himmelfarb, John, 1995-2001 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Hinds, Rene, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Hinebrook, Michelle, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Hines, Tobin, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Hinojosa, Juan, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Hipwell, Michael, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- HIRO, NAOTAKA, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Hiromi, Niizeki, 1995-2001 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Hirose, Yuriko, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Hirsch, Antonia, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Hirsch, Callie Danae, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Hirsch, Debora, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Hirschl, Tamar, 2003-2005 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Hitchcock, Leanne, 1990-1991 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Hitner, Chuck, 1991-2004 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Hitt, Jay, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Hlavina, Tomas, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Ho, Christopher, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Ho, Colleen, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Hoberman, Norman, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Hobson, Mary Daniel, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Hodes, Suzanne, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Hodge, Chris, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Hodge, Mary, 1995-1999 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Hodges, Jennifer, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Hodges, Suzanne, 1994-2004 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Hoeber, Ditta Baron, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Hoepfner, Karla, 2001-2003 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Hoey, Wayne, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Hoferer, Marietta, 1989-2000 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Hoffman, Eileen, 1992-2001 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Hoffmann, Bettina, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Hoffman, Wendy, 1987-1989 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Hofmann, Melanie, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Hofverberg, Anna, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Hogg, Corrie, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- Hoguet, Deidre, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Hohenberg, Laetitia, 1992-1997 (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Holleman, Kim, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Hollender, Eric, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Hollister, Paul, 1975-1989 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Holmes, Holly, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Holmes, Robyn, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Holsinger, Jayne, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Holst, Mamie, 1991-1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Holt, Sara, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Holt, Warren, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Holten, Katie, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Holub, Joel, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Holwerda-Williams, Gloria, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Holze, Jeannie, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Holzfeind, Heidrun, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Holzworth, Lawrence, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Honeycutt, Brece, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Hong, Kathleen, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Hong, Young Sook, 1994-1998 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Hongisto, Eric, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Hoogenboom, Jan, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Hooper, Cassandra, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Hopper, Carol, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Hornbeck, Carrie, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Hornick, Andrea, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Hornor, Dave, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Horochowski, Alexa, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 27)
- Horowitz, Albert, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Hoshine, Kenichi, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Hoskins, Moses, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Houghton, Jarrod, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Houlberg, Mia Lor, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Houng, Gloria, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Houser, Page, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Houshmand, Roshan, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Housman, Elaine, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Houston, Nancy, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Hovey, Karrie, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Howard, Ami, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Howard, Katie, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Howard, Ronald, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Howard-Levy, Alison, 1994-2001 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Howell, Elise, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Hrbacek, Mary, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Hsiao, Gilbert, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Hsieh, Victor, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Hu, Klaus, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Huang, Chennie, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Huang, Natalie, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Huang, Wennie, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Hubard, Olga, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Huber, Roswitha, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Hudders, William, 1992-2001 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Hudock, Tina, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Hudson, Jon Barlow, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Huey, Elizabeth, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Hughes, Christine, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Hughes, Farida, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- Hughes, Laura, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Hulen, Jeannie, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- Hull, Timothy, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Humphrey, Sheryl, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 53)
- Hunter, Nikita, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 54)
- Hunter, Stephen, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- Huntington, Jeff, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- Hupfel, Gretchen, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 57)
- Huskey, Trevor, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 77)
- Hutchins, Mary, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 58)
- Hutter, Richard, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 59)
- Hutzell, Jain, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- Hwang, Eunjung, 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- Hypaa, Bradley Lucas, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 62)
- Hyunri, Kim, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 94)
- Hwang, Nancy, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Hyde, Budge, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Hydes, Bendel, 1993-2000 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Iaboni, Lisa, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Ibbott, Stephen, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 64)
- Ichikawa, Akiko, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 65)
- Idele, Wendy, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 66)
- Iff, Florence, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 67)
- Ighile, Osaretin, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 68)
- Igloria, Regin, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 69)
- Iida, Yoko, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 82)
- Iijima, Isao, 1992-1994 (Box 61, Folder 78)
- Ikens, Curt, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 70)
- Iliatova, Vera, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Illig, Peter, 1998-2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Imai, Taeko, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 79)
- Imatani, Garrick, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Imhoff, Cindy, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Infante, Santa, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Ingalls, Asia, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Ingraham, Susan, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Inoue, Ryuji, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Insogna, Elizabeth, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Ioannidou, Ketta, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Irvine, Andy, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Irwin, Jane, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Isaacs, Barbara, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Isbister, Arnold James, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Isenhour, David, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Ishida, Jun'ichiro, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Ishikawa, Minako, 1992-2004 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Ishino, Mayumi, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Itagaki, Yoshio, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Ivanoff, Peter, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Ivanova, Anna, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Ivins, Tara, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Iwamura, Minako, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Jacimovic, Milos, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Jack, James, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Jackson, Clarke, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Jackson, Grant, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Jackson, Ianthe, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Jackson, Jed, 1984-1989 (Box 61, Folder 80)
- Jackson, Laurie, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Jacobs, Hedwige, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 77)
- Jacobs, Holger, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Jacobs, Peter, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Jacobsmeyer, John, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Jacobsohn, Rosemary, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Jacobson, Leah A., 1990-1992 (Box 61, Folder 81)
- Jadlocki, CJ, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Jaffe, Michelle, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Jager, Britta Melanie, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Jahncke, Chris, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Jahnig, Ross, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Jain, Vandana, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- James, Jimmie, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- James, Monica Lynn, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- James, Richard, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Jameson, Gary, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Janairo Roth, Yumi, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Jancso, Kata, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Jang, Hey-yeun, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Janitz, Robert, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Janowski, Karyn, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Jans, Stefan, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- JAO, Julie, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Jarski, Elsa, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 56)
- Jarvis, Steve, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Jaxxa, James, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Jaye, Nena, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Jean Francois, Muller, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Jeffers, Jim, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Jejina, Ingrid, 1998-2002 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Jelsma, Amparo, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Jenkins, Jennifer, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 47)